<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="food_blog">
<b>1. Grapes and Olives</b>\n<br/>
    If you are looking to have a beautiful view of the entire swansea city, this place must be visited. It is located near the city center and is in the highest building in Swansea (28 storey high).<br/><br/>

2. Govinda\'s\n <br/>
    For the vegans and vegetarians amongst you, this Hare Krishna-run café has a great menu with snacks starting at £1.50 and mains starting at £3.75, meaning students won’t be out of pocket. The eggless mayo is said to be delicious and their daily menu includes popular dishes like moussaka, aubergine bake, pasta dishes, dahls and pizza. The décor is basic and somewhat out-dated but that doesn’t detract from its relaxing atmosphere. Even the carnivores out there might be persuaded to convert after eating here!

3. The Uplands Diner\n <br/>
	This place is truly one of the top student restaurants in Swansea, it fills students dream with a multitude of cheap breakfast options including ‘Builder’s Load’, ‘Uplands Special’ and ‘Diner’s Delight’. They also offer classic avocado dishes as well as eggs benedict, royale and Americano! If you and your mates are suffering the hangover from hell, why not attempt the Mega Beast, which comes in at £12.50? Make sure you’re hungry for 10 rashers of bacon, 5 eggs, 8 sausages, chips, 2 hash browns, bubble and squeak, mushrooms, tomatoes, beans, 2 pieces of black pudding, 4 pieces of toast, 4 slices of bread and butter, 4 pieces of fried bread and 1 small burger. That’ll keep you going for a while.

4. VERDI’S\n
	Located in Swansea Bay, Mumbles, this beachfront café has glass walls, making the views from whichever table you choose to sit at breath taking. The ice cream and gelato on offer here is to die for and made fresh every day from local produce. They also offer a great range of sandwiches (all around £5) and bigger dishes such as pizza, pasta and salads.

5. Rose Indienne\n
	Rose Indienne is a smart modern curry house that lets you dine for under a tenner!As one of Swansea’s top 10 student restaurants, the food is incredible and if you’re feeling peckish on a Sunday head down to their all you can eat buffet priced at £9.95 per person! They also offer a 10% discount on takeaways when you collect them – your student pocket will thank you for the extra walk!

    </string>

</resources>